Guide to the Herbert Feigl Papers, 1916-1973 ASP.1997.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Writings by Feigl, 1927-1971; IV.
  - Papers by Herbert Feigl, 1927-1971; 2.
    - "The Significance of Physics in Man's Philosophy", 1939 (Folder 61)
    - "Some Crucial Issues of Mind-Body Monism", 1971 (Folder 62)
    - "Some General Afterthoughts on Your Autobiography", 1957 (Folder 63)
    - "Some Issues of Scientific Humanism", 1959, 1961 (Folder 64)
    - "Some Notes on Causality" (Folder 65)
    - "Some Remarks on the Meaning of Scientific Explanation" (Folder 66)
    - "Some Remarks on the Meaning of Value Judgements" (Folder 67)
    - "Space, Time and Relativity" (Folder 68)
    - "Tentative Remarks on 'Observables', 'Unobservables', and Alternatives of Epistemological Reconstruction", 1955 (Folder 69)
    - "Las Tesis del Empirismo Logico", 1964 (Folder 70)
    - "Toward a Philosophy for Our Age of Science", 1961, 1963, 1965 (Folder 71)
    - "Towards a Philosophy of Intellectual Maturity", 1956 (Folder 72)
    - "Types of Concepts and Types of Definitions in Psychology" (Folder 73)
    - "Über die Leistung des hypothetisch-konstruktiven Denkens in den Naturwissenschaften", 1956 (Folder 74)
    - "Unity of Science and Unitary Science", 1939 (Folder 75)
    - "Unity of Science vs. Unity of Knowledge", 1969 (Folder 76)
    - "Validation and Vindication", 1951 (Folder 77)
    - "Vienna Circle" (Folder 78)
    - "What Hume Might Have Said to Kant" (Folder 79)
    - "What Is, and What is Not, Cognitively Significant", 1954 (Folder 80)
    - "Die Wissenschaft als Instrument zur Vorhersage und zur Gestaltung der Zukunft", 1961 (Folder 81)
    - "Wissenschaft, Erfahrung, Metaphysik", 1966 (Reel 10, Folder 82)
    - "Wissenschaftliche Weltauffassung der Wiener Kreis", 1929 (Folder 83)
    - "Zufall und Gesetz", 1928 (Folder 84)
- Writings by Others, 1916-1972; V.
  This series covers writings by other researchers and colleagues mostly relating to scientific philosophy. The manuscripts are arranged alphabetically by the author's last name.
  - Abelson, Raziel (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Alexander, H. Gavin I (Folder 2)
  - Alexander H. Gavin II, 1956-1957 (Folder 3)
  - Anderson, Robert, 1972 (Folder 4)
  - Anderson V. Elving (Folder 5)
  - Arnaud (Folder 6)
  - Aune, Bruce I (Folder 7)
  - Aune, Bruce II, 1960 (Folder 8)
  - Aune, Bruce III (Folder 9)
  - Aune, Bruce IV (Folder 10)
  - Ayer, A. J. (Folder 11)
  - Baier, Kurt (Folder 12)
  - Bartley, W. W., III (Folder 13)
  - Baumer, William H., 1966 (Folder 14)
  - Bergmann, Gustav, 1955 (Folder 15)
  - Berlin, I., 1950 (Folder 16)
  - Birnabum, Allan, 1962 (Folder 17)
  - Black, Max I (Folder 18)
  - Black, Max II (Folder 19)
  - Blumberg, A. (Folder 20)
  - Bohnert, Herbert Gaylord I, 1961 (Folder 21)
  - Bohnert, Herbert Gaylord II, 1955 (Folder 22)
  - Born, Max I, 1953 (Folder 23)
  - Born, Max II, 1953 (Folder 24)
  - Bradford, Norman (Folder 25)
  - Bradley, Ray D. (Folder 26)
  - Broad, C. D. (Folder 27)
  - Brodbeck, May I, 1960 (Folder 28)
  - Brodbeck, May II, 1958 (Folder 29)
  - Brodbeck, May III, 1953 (Folder 30)
  - Brodbeck, May IV, 1964 (Folder 31)
  - Brunswik, Egon, 1953-1954 (Folder 32)
  - Bub, Jeffrey I (Folder 33)
  - Bub, Jeffrey II (Folder 34)
  - Buck, Roger C. (Folder 35)
  - Burks, Arthur I, 1954 (Folder 36)
  - Burks, Arthur II (Folder 37)
  - Burks, Arthur III, 1962 (Folder 38)
  - Campbell, Donald T. (Folder 39)
  - Campbell, Keith (Folder 40)
  - Carnap, Rudolf I, 1956 (Folder 41)
  - Carnap, Rudolf II, 1955-1965 (Reel 11, Folder 42)
  - Carnap, Rudolf III, 1954-1969 (Folder 43)
  - Carnap, Rudolf IV, 1960 (Folder 44)
  - Carnap, Rudolf V, 1954-1957 (Folder 45)
  - Carnap, Rudolf VI, 1957-1962 (Folder 46)
  - Carnap, Rudolf VII (Folder 47)
  - Carnap, Rudolf VIII (Folder 48)
  - Carnap, Rudolf IX, 1955 (Folder 49)
  - Carnap, Rudolf X (Folder 50)
  - Carnap, Rudolf XI, 1954 (Folder 51)
  - Carnap, Rudolf XII, 1954-1962 (Folder 52)
  - Carnap, Rudolf XIII, 1957 (Folder 53)
  - Carnap, Rudolf XIV, 1954 (Folder 54)
  - Carnap, Rudolf XV, 1955 (Folder 55)
  - Carnap, Rudolf XVI, 1954-1956 (Folder 56)
  - Carnap, Rudolf XVII, 1957 (Folder 57)
  - Chapin, F. Stuart (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Chappell, John E., 1971 (Folder 2)
  - Chung-ying Cheng (Folder 3)
  - Church, Alonzo (Folder 4)
  - Colby, Kenneth Mark, 1970 (Folder 5)
  - Coleman, Francis J. (Folder 6)
  - Cornman, James W. (Folder 7)
  - Cudmore, Ann, 1970 (Folder 8)
  - Demopoulis, William I, 1966 (Folder 9)
  - Demopoulis, William II, 1967 (Folder 10)
  - Demopoulis, William III (Folder 11)
  - Dulany, Don E., 1966 (Folder 12)
  - Economos, Judith (Reel 12, Folder 13)
  - Ekstein, Rudolf (Folder 14)
  - Ellis, Albert, 1949 (Folder 15)
  - Ellis, Brian (Folder 16)
  - Everett, Millard S. I, 1963 (Folder 17)
  - Everett, Millard S. II (Folder 18)
  - Everett, MIllard S. III (Folder 19)
  - Falk, John L. (Folder 20)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. I (Folder 21)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. II (Folder 22)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. III (Folder 23)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. IV (Folder 24)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. V (Folder 25)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. VI (Folder 26)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. VII (Folder 27)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. VIII, 1954 (Folder 28)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. IX, 1963 (Folder 29)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. X (Reel 13, Folder 30)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. XI (Folder 31)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. XII, 1955-1957 (Folder 32)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. XIII, 1957-1959 (Folder 33)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. XIV, 1957-1963 (Folder 34)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. XV, 1957 (Folder 35)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. XVI, 1965-1969 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K. XVII (Folder 2)
  - Finn, D. R. (Folder 3)
  - Flew, Anthony, 1954 (Folder 4)
  - Fritz, Charles A. (Folder 5)
  - Galanter, Eugene H. (Folder 6)
  - Gal-Or, Benjamin, 1970-1971 (Folder 7)
  - Garver, J. Newton (Folder 8)
  - Gierer, Alfred (Folder 9)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf I (Folder 10)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf II, 1957 (Folder 11)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf III (Folder 12)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf IV, 1957 (Folder 13)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf V, 1958 (Folder 14)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf VI, 1959-1960 (Folder 15)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf VII, 1953-1962 (Folder 16)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf VIII, 1957-1963 (Folder 17)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf IX (Folder 18)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf X, 1958 (Folder 19)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf XI, 1955-1956 (Reel 14, Folder 20)
  - Grunberg, Emile (Folder 21)
  - Gunderson, Keith I (Folder 22)
  - Gunderson, Keith II (Folder 23)
  - Gunderson, Keith III (Folder 24)
  - Gunderson, Keith IV, 1967 (Folder 25)
  - Hampshire, Stuart (Folder 26)
  - Hanson, Norwood Russell I, 1958 (Folder 27)
  - Hanson, Norwood Russell II (Folder 28)
  - Hanson, Norwood Russell III (Folder 29)
  - Hanson, Norwood Russell IV (Folder 30)
  - Hanson, Norwood Russell V (Folder 31)
  - Hanson, Norwood Russell VI, 1963 (Folder 32)
  - Hanson, Norwood Russell VII (Folder 33)
  - Harris, Errol E. (Folder 34)
  - Hayek, F. A. von (Folder 35)
  - Helmer, Olaf (Folder 36)
  - Hempel, Carl G. I (Folder 37)
  - Hempel, Carl G. II (Folder 38)
  - Hempel, Carl G. III (Folder 39)
  - Hesse, Mary I (Folder 40)
  - Hesse, Mary II (Folder 41)
  - Hill, E. L. (Folder 42)
  - Hinshaw, Virgil G., Jr. (Folder 43)
  - Hintikka, Jaakko (Folder 44)
  - Hobart, R. E. (Folder 45)
  - Holmer, Paul L. (Folder 46)
  - Hospers, John (Folder 47)
  - Humburg, Jürgen (Folder 48)
  - Hurwicz, Leonid (Folder 49)
  - Kaplan, Abraham (Folder 50)
  - Kekes, John (Folder 51)
  - Kemeny, John C., 1956 (Folder 52)
  - Kielkopf, C. (Folder 53)
  - Kneale, William (Folder 54)
  - Koch, S. (Folder 55)
  - Kraft, Victor I (Folder 56)
  - Kraft, Victor II (Folder 57)
  - Kraft, Victor III (Folder 58)
  - Lachs, John, 1963 (Folder 59)
  - Lackner, Henry I, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Lackner, Henry II (Folder 2)
  - Lakatos, Imre, 1970 (Folder 3)
  - Landé, Alfred, 1959 (Folder 4)
  - Laudan, Larry (Reel 15, Folder 5)
  - Lazarsfeld, Paul F. I (Folder 6)
  - Lazarsfeld, Paul F. II (Folder 7)
  - Leeper, Robert, 1949 (Folder 8)
  - Lenzen, V. (Folder 9)
  - Lewis, Clarence I, 1952 (Folder 10)
  - Lindzey, Gardner (Folder 11)
  - Lipscomb, William N. (Folder 12)
  - Lundberg, George A., 1952 (Folder 13)
  - Mackay, D. M., 1957 (Folder 14)
  - Mackinnon, D. M. (Folder 15)
  - McMullin, Ernan I (Folder 16)
  - McMullin, Ernan II (Folder 17)
  - McMullin, Ernan III (Folder 18)
  - McMullin, Ernan IV (Folder 19)
  - McMullin, Ernan V (Folder 20)
  - McMullin, Ernan VI (Folder 21)
  - McMullin, Ernan VII (Folder 22)
  - McMullin, Ernan VIII (Folder 23)
  - Malcolm, Norman (Folder 24)
  - Maruyama, Magoroh (Folder 25)
  - Maslow, A. H. (Folder 26)
  - Massey, Gerald J. (Folder 27)
  - Matthews, Gareth B., 1965 (Folder 28)
  - Maxwell, Grover I (Folder 29)
  - Maxwell, Grover II, 1963-1965 (Folder 30)
  - Maxwell, Grover III, 1955-1968 (Folder 31)
  - Meehl, Paul E. I, 1955-1966 (Folder 32)
  - Meehl, Paul E. II, 1967 (Folder 33)
  - Meehl, Paul E. III (Folder 34)
  - Meehl, Paul E. IV, 1961 (Folder 35)
  - Meehl, Paul E. V, 1951-1966 (Folder 36)
  - Meehl, Paul E. VI, 1954-1959 (Folder 37)
  - Meehl, Paul E. VII, 1955 (Folder 38)
  - Meehl, Paul E. VIII, 1951 (Folder 39)
  - Meehl, Paul E. IX, 1954 (Folder 40)
  - Meehl, Paul E. X, 1951 (Folder 41)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XI, 1958 (Folder 42)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XII, 1951 (Folder 43)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XIII, 1954 (Folder 44)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XIV, 1954 (Folder 45)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XV, 1954 (Folder 46)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XVI, 1950 (Folder 47)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XVII, 1950-1954 (Folder 48)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XVIII, 1951-1956 (Folder 49)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XIX (Folder 50)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XX (Folder 51)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XXI (Folder 52)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XXII (Reel 16, Folder 53)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XXIII (Folder 54)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XXIV, 1960-1969 (Folder 55)
  - Meehl, Paul E. XXV, 1961 (Folder 56)
  - Mehlberg, Henryk I, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Mehlberg, Henryk II (Folder 2)
  - Mehlberg, Henryk III (Folder 3)
  - Mehlberg, Henryk IV (Folder 4)
  - Mehlberg, Henryk V (Folder 5)
  - Mehlberg, Henryk VI (Folder 6)
  - Mehlberg, Henryk VII, 1956 (Folder 7)
  - Menger, Karl, 1966 (Folder 8)
  - Merton, Robert K., 1945 (Folder 9)
  - Miller, Dickinson S., 1929 (Folder 10)
  - Miller, Neal E., 1955 (Folder 11)
  - Montague, Richard, 1964-1967 (Folder 12)
  - Morris, Charles (Folder 13)
  - Mosteller, Frederick, 1952 (Folder 14)
  - Murphy, Jeffrie G. (Folder 15)
  - Myro, George (Folder 16)
  - Nagel, Ernest I, 1952 (Folder 17)
  - Nagel, Ernest II (Folder 18)
  - Nagel, Ernest III, 1949 (Folder 19)
  - Natkin, Marcel (Folder 20)
  - Nelson, Everett J. (Folder 21)
  - Nolan, Rita (Folder 22)
  - Oppenheim, Paul, 1954 (Folder 23)
  - Pap, Arthur I (Folder 24)
  - Pap, Arthur II, 1951-1959 (Folder 25)
  - Pap, Arthur III, 1955 (Folder 26)
  - Pap, Arthur IV, 1951-1955 (Reel 17, Folder 27)
  - Pepper, Stephen C. I, 1926 (Folder 28)
  - Pepper, Stephen C. II (Folder 29)
  - Pepper, Stephen C. III (Folder 30)
  - Perry, Ralph Barton, 1916 (Folder 31)
  - Pike, Kenneth L., 1959 (Folder 32)
  - Popper, Karl R. I, 1955 (Folder 33)
  - Popper, Karl R. II, 1953 (Folder 34)
  - Popper, Karl R. III, 1960 (Folder 35)
  - Popper, Karl R. IV, 1959 (Folder 36)
  - Popper, Karl R. V (Folder 37)
  - Manuscripts -- Popper, Karl R. VI, 1956 (Folder 38)
  - Popper, Karl R. VII (Folder 39)
  - Popper, Karl R. VIII, 1945 (Folder 40)
  - Popper, Karl R. IX (Folder 41)
  - Postman, Leo (Folder 42)
  - Potter, K. H., 1969 (Folder 43)
  - Price, H. H. (Folder 44)
  - Putnam, Hilary I, 1957 (Folder 45)
  - Putnam, Hilary II, 1961 (Folder 46)
  - Putnam, Hilary III, 1954-1959 (Folder 47)
  - Putnam, Hilary IV, 1956 (Folder 48)
  - Putnam, Hilary V, 1956 (Folder 49)
  - Putnam, Hilary VI, 1957 (Folder 50)
  - Putnam, Hilary VII, 1961 (Folder 51)
  - Putnam, Hilary VIII (Folder 52)
  - Quine, W. V. O. I, 1951 (Folder 53)
  - Quine, W. V. O. II, 1948-1957 (Folder 54)
  - Raab, Francis V., 1960 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Rand, Rose (Folder 2)
  - Razran, Gregory, 1957 (Folder 3)
  - Reichenbach, Hans I, 1952 (Folder 4)
  - Reichenbach, Hans II (Folder 5)
  - Reid, John R. (Folder 6)
  - Rescher, Nicholas, 1954 (Folder 7)
  - Richfield, Jerome (Folder 8)
  - Riegel, Klaus F., 1971 (Folder 9)
  - Ritchie, Benbow F. (Folder 10)
  - Rose, Arnold M. (Folder 11)
  - Ross, Ralph, 1954 (Folder 12)
  - Rothstein, Jermone, 1951-1952 (Folder 13)
  - Routley, Richard (Folder 14)
  - Rozeboom, William W. I, 1957-1959 (Folder 15)
  - Rozeboom, William W. II, 1956 (Folder 16)
  - Rozeboom, William W. III, 1958 (Folder 17)
  - Rozeboom, William W. IV, 1971 (Reel 18, Folder 18)
  - Rozeboom, William W. V, 1957-1958 (Folder 19)
  - Rozeboom, William W. VI, 1958-1960 (Folder 20)
  - Rozeboom, William W. VII, 1956-1957 (Folder 21)
  - Rynin, D. (Folder 22)
  - Salmon, Wesley C. I, 1956 (Folder 23)
  - Salmon, Wesley C. II, 1964 (Folder 24)
  - Schaffner, Kenneth F. (Folder 25)
  - Scher, Jordan M. (Folder 26)
  - Scherer, Donald (Folder 27)
  - Schlegel, Richard I, 1967 (Folder 28)
  - Schlegel, Richard II (Folder 29)
  - Schlesinger, George I, 1964-1967 (Folder 30)
  - Schlesinger, George II (Folder 31)
  - Schuetz, Alfred, 1952 (Folder 32)
  - Scriven, Michael I (Folder 33)
  - Scriven, Michael II, 1957 (Folder 34)
  - Scriven, Michael III (Folder 35)
  - Scriven, Michael IV, 1954-1959 (Folder 36)
  - Scriven, Michael V (Folder 37)
  - Scriven, Michael VI, 1953-1955 (Folder 38)
  - Sellars, Roy W. I (Folder 39)
  - Sellars, Roy W. II (Folder 40)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid I, 1954, 1958, 1964 (Folder 41)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid II (Folder 42)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid III (Folder 43)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid IV (Folder 44)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid V, 1954-1963 (Folder 45)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid VI, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid VII, 1957 (Folder 2)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid VIII (Reel 19, Folder 3)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid IX, 1953-1954 (Folder 4)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid X, 1953-1957 (Folder 5)
  - Settle, Thomas W., 1965 (Folder 6)
  - Shapere, Dudley, 1965 (Folder 7)
  - Sharpless, Seth I, 1955 (Folder 8)
  - Sharpless, Seth II, 1955 (Folder 9)
  - Skinner, B. F., 1953 (Folder 10)
  - Smart, J. J. C. I, 1961 (Folder 11)
  - Smart, J. J. C. II, 1963 (Folder 12)
  - Smart, J. J. C. III, 1956 (Folder 13)
  - Smart, J. J. C. IV, 1961 (Folder 14)
  - Smart, J. J. C. V, 1963-1965 (Folder 15)
  - Sosensky, Irving (Folder 16)
  - Spence, K. W. (Folder 17)
  - Sperry, R. W., 1969 (Folder 18)
  - Stegmüller, Wolfgang, 1970 (Folder 19)
  - Stein, Howard I (Folder 20)
  - Stein, Howard II, 1967 (Folder 21)
  - Stout, A. K. (Folder 22)
  - Stoutland, F. M. (Folder 23)
  - Strawson, P. F. I (Folder 24)
  - Strawson, P. F. II, 1956 (Folder 25)
  - Suppes, Patrick I (Folder 26)
  - Suppes, Patrick II, 1955 (Folder 27)
  - Suppes, Patrick III, 1955 (Folder 28)
  - Tolman, Edward C. (Folder 29)
  - Törnebohm, Hakan (Folder 30)
  - Toulmin, Stephen, 1960 (Folder 31)
  - Trotter, J. R. (Folder 32)
  - Urbach, Franz, 1929 (Folder 33)
  - van der Ziel, A. (Folder 34)
  - van Fraassen, Bas C. (Folder 35)
  - Visvader, J. (Folder 36)
  - Walker, Evan Harris (Folder 37)
  - Walker, Stanley, 1935-1938 (Folder 38)
  - Watanabe, Satosi (Folder 39)
  - White, Willie (Folder 40)
  - Wilson, Fred (Folder 41)
  - Winnie, John A. (Reel 20, Folder 42)
  - Wisdom, J. O. I, 1970 (Folder 43)
  - Wisdom, J. O. II, 1953-1969 (Folder 44)
  - Wold, Herman O. A., 1957-1958 (Folder 45)
  - Zener, Karl (Folder 46)
  - Ziff, Paul (Folder 47)
  - Zweig, Arnulf (Folder 48)
  - Unidentified I (Folder 49)
  - Unidentified II (Folder 50)
  - Unidentified III, 1966 (Folder 51)
- Offprints by Others, 1903-1980; VI.
  This series contains offprints of published articles by others, arranged alpabetically by the author's last name.
  - Abraham, William E., 1969 (Reel 20, Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Achinstein, Peter, 1964-1965 (Folder 2)
  - Agassi, Joseph, 1959-1966 (Folder 3)
  - Aiken, Henry David, 1947 (Folder 4)
  - Alston, William P. (Folder 5)
  - Aris, Rutherford, 1969-1970 (Folder 6)
  - Armstrong, D. M., 1969 (Folder 7)
  - Asch, Solomon E., 1968 (Folder 8)
  - Axinn, Sidney, 1968 (Folder 9)
  - Ayer, A. J., 1960, 1967 (Folder 10)
  - Baldus, Richard, 1924 (Folder 11)
  - Bar-Hillel, Y., 1957 (Folder 12)
  - Bartley, W. W., III, 1962, 1965, 1969 (Folder 13)
  - Baumer, William H., 1969 (Folder 14)
  - Beck, Lewis White, 1950 (Folder 15)
  - Bergmann, Gustav, 1956-1980 (Folder 16)
  - Bernfeld, Siegfried, 1930 (Folder 17)
  - Bernhard, Robert, 1968 (Folder 18)
  - Bertalanffy, Ludwig von, 1937 (Folder 19)
  - Birnbaum, Allan, 1961 (Folder 20)
  - Biser, Erwin, 1953 (Folder 21)
  - Black, Max (Folder 22)
  - Blanshard, Brand, 1955 (Folder 23)
  - Bohm, David J., 1963-1966 (Folder 24)
  - Boring, Edwin G., 1955-1957 (Folder 25)
  - Born, M., 1956 (Folder 26)
  - Brandt, Richard B., 1955, 1969 (Folder 27)
  - Brèhier, Emile, 1948 (Folder 28)
  - Brodbeck, May, 1960-1966 (Folder 29)
  - Brunswik, Egon, 1955 (Folder 30)
  - Bunge, Mario, 1955-1956, 1960, 1967, 1969-1970 (Folder 31)
  - Burks, Arthur W., 1963 (Folder 32)
  - Campbell, Donald T., 1964 (Folder 33)
  - Campbell, Keith, 1965 (Folder 34)
  - Carnap, Rudolf, 1925, 1927, 1946, 1958, 1961, 1963 (Folder 35)
  - Caruth, Elaine, 1968 (Folder 36)
  - Chandler, Hugh S., 1968 (Folder 37)
  - Chisholm, Roderick M., 1955 (Folder 38)
  - Church, Alonzo, 1943 (Folder 39)
  - Close, Elizabeth S., 1962 (Folder 40)
  - Coan, Richard W., 1964 (Folder 41)
  - Coleman, Francis J., 1964 (Folder 42)
  - Colodny, Robert G., 1972 (Folder 43)
  - Cornman, James W., 1962-1971 (Folder 44)
  - Davidson, Donald, 1967-1969 (Reel 21, Folder 45)
  - Dedekind, Richard, 1912, 1923 (Folder 46)
  - Dewey, John, 1909 (Folder 47)
  - Eccles, John, Sir., 1965 (Folder 48)
  - Edel, Abraham, 1964 (Folder 49)
  - Edwards, Paul, 1967 (Folder 50)
  - Einstein, Albert, 1936 (Folder 51)
  - Ekstein, Rudolf, 1961 (Folder 52)
  - Essler, Wilhelm Karl, 1970 (Folder 53)
  - Everett, Millard S., 1963 (Folder 54)
  - Feyerabend, Paul, 1952-1964 (Folder 55)
  - Feynman, Richard P., 1966 (Folder 56)
  - Firth, Roderick, 1950 (Folder 57)
  - Frege, Gottlob, 1948, 1950 (Folder 58)
  - Fritz, Charles A., Jr. (Folder 59)
  - Gellner, Ernest, 1968 (Folder 60)
  - Gill, John C., 1961 (Folder 61)
  - Glashow, W. D., 1968 (Folder 62)
  - Gödel, Kurt, 1951 (Folder 63)
  - Goe, George, 1962-1970 (Folder 64)
  - Goldman, Alvin I., 1967 (Folder 65)
  - Goodman, Nelson, 1967 (Folder 66)
  - Görland, A., 1911 (Folder 67)
  - Gottesman, I. I., 1968 (Folder 68)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf, 1955-1969 (Folder 69)
  - Häberlin, Paul, 1921 (Folder 70)
  - Hahn, Hans, 1930 (Folder 71)
  - Handlin, Oscar, 1971 (Folder 72)
  - Hansel, C. E. M., 1967 (Folder 73)
  - Hanson, N. R., 1960 (Folder 74)
  - Hare, R. M., 1963 (Folder 75)
  - Harrell, Rafael Ruiz, 1961 (Folder 76)
  - Hartshorne, Charles, 1967 (Folder 77)
  - Hayek, Friedrich A. von, 1965 (Folder 78)
  - Hempel, Carl G., 1962 (Folder 79)
  - Henle, Paul, 1948 (Folder 80)
  - Herbst, P., 1957 (Folder 81)
  - Hesse, Mary, 1962-1970 (Folder 82)
  - Hintikka, Jaakko, 1970 (Folder 83)
  - Hobart, R. E., 1934 (Reel 21, Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Hofstadter, Albert, 1955 (Folder 2)
  - Holton, Gerald, 1965 (Folder 3)
  - Honorton, Charles, 1967 (Folder 4)
  - Hood, Albert B., 1964 (Folder 5)
  - Hook, Sidney, 1954 (Folder 6)
  - Hopkins, Jasper, 1968 (Folder 7)
  - Ichheiser, Gustav, 1966 (Folder 8)
  - Immergluck, Ludwig, 1964 (Folder 9)
  - Jaki, Stanley L., 1967 (Folder 10)
  - Jarvie, I. C., 1964 (Folder 11)
  - Jenkins, Iredell, 1950 (Folder 12)
  - Juhos, Béla, 1964-1970 (Folder 13)
  - Kaila, Enio, 1936 (Folder 14)
  - Kaplan, A., 1950 (Folder 15)
  - Kawada, Kumataro (Folder 16)
  - Kekes, John, 1971 (Folder 17)
  - Kemeny, John G., 1960 (Folder 18)
  - Kilgore, William J., 1965 (Folder 19)
  - Kim, Jaegwon, 1966 (Folder 20)
  - Kitts, David B., 1963 (Folder 21)
  - Kleinpeter, Hans, 1903 (Folder 22)
  - Köhler, Wolfgang, 1955 (Folder 23)
  - Kraft, Viktor, 1926, 1969-1970 (Reel 22, Folder 24)
  - Lakatos, Imre, 1968 (Folder 25)
  - Lamont, Corliss, 1970 (Folder 26)
  - Landé, Alfred, 1967-1969 (Folder 27)
  - Langer, Susanne K., 1927 (Folder 28)
  - Lehrer, Keith, 1970 (Folder 29)
  - Leinfellner, Werner, 1966-1968 (Folder 30)
  - Lindworsky, J., 1922, 1926 (Folder 31)
  - Lloyd, G. E. R., 1968 (Folder 32)
  - McCarthy, Harold E., 1956 (Folder 33)
  - McClosky, Herbert, 1949 (Folder 34)
  - MacCorquodale, Kenneth, 1970 (Folder 35)
  - McGuire, Martin C., 1963 (Folder 36)
  - Machlup, Fritz, 1964 (Folder 37)
  - McLaughlin, Andrew, 1970 (Folder 38)
  - McMullin, Ernan, 1966, 1968, 1970 (Folder 39)
  - Madden, Edward H., 1970-1971 (Folder 40)
  - Mandelbaum, Maurice (Folder 41)
  - Margenau, Henry, 1954-1970 (Folder 42)
  - Maslow, A. H. (Folder 43)
  - Mates, Benson, 1950-1951 (Folder 44)
  - Matthews, Gareth B., 1967 (Folder 45)
  - Meehl, Paul E., 1956-1970 (Folder 46)
  - Mehlberg, Henryk, 1960 (Folder 47)
  - Meinong, Alexius, 1913 (Folder 48)
  - Meister, Richard, 1927-1928 (Folder 49)
  - Menger, Karl, 1938 (Folder 50)
  - Merton, Robert K., 1948 (Folder 51)
  - Miller, David, 1968 (Folder 52)
  - Miller, Dickinson S., 1929 (Folder 53)
  - Morris, Charles, 1960-1965 (Folder 54)
  - Mowrer, O. Hobart, 1965 (Folder 55)
  - Mueller-Deham, Albert, 1944 (Folder 56)
  - Mulder, H. L., 1968 (Folder 57)
  - Nagel, Ernest, 1939, 1963, 1968 (Folder 58)
  - Nelson, Benjamin, 1968 (Folder 59)
  - Neurath, Otto, 1935 (Folder 60)
  - Newell, A., 1957 (Folder 61)
  - Odegaard, Charles E., 1952 (Folder 62)
  - Oppenheim, Paul, 1961, 1967, 1969 (Folder 63)
  - Osgood, Charles E., 1958 (Folder 64)
  - Pap, Arthur, 1952, 1954, 1958 (Folder 65)
  - Passmore, John, 1962 (Folder 66)
  - Pedoe, Daniel, 1970 (Folder 67)
  - Perelman, Chaim, 1955 (Folder 68)
  - Perkins, Moreland, 1965 (Folder 69)
  - Planck, Max, 1930 (Reel 23, Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Platt, John R., 1968-1969 (Folder 2)
  - Polanyi, Michael, 1961-1969 (Folder 3)
  - Popper, Karl R., 1957-1968 (Folder 4)
  - Price, H. H., 1949 (Folder 5)
  - Putnam, HIlary, 1957, 1962 (Folder 6)
  - Quine, Willard V. O., 1943, 1951 (Folder 7)
  - Rankin, K. W., 1964, 1968 (Folder 8)
  - Rauscher, Josef, 1958, 1962 (Folder 9)
  - Reichenbach, Hans, 1936, 1937, 1953 (Folder 10)
  - Rescher, Nicholas, 1958-1959 (Folder 11)
  - Rie, Robert, 1962 (Folder 12)
  - Roper, Jame E., 1965 (Folder 13)
  - Ross, John, 1965 (Folder 14)
  - Ross, Ralph, 1968 (Folder 15)
  - Salmon, Wesley C., 1953-1970 (Folder 16)
  - Sartorius, Rolf, 1969 (Folder 17)
  - Schaffner, Kenneth F. (Folder 18)
  - Scheffler, Israel, 1950 (Folder 19)
  - Schilpp, Paul A., 1929, 1948 (Folder 20)
  - Schlegel, Richard, 1950, 1970 (Folder 21)
  - Schlesinger, G., 1967, 1969 (Folder 22)
  - Schneider, Joseph, 1945 (Folder 23)
  - Scriven, Michael, 1956, 1959, 1966 (Folder 24)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid, 1947, 1954, 1965 (Folder 25)
  - Semmes, Josephine, 1966 (Folder 26)
  - Shotwell, Thomas K., 1965 (Folder 28)
  - Simon, Herbert A. (Folder 29)
  - Shaffer, Jerome A., 1965 (Folder 27)
  - Simon, Walter B., 1963 (Folder 30)
  - Simons, Leo, 1962 (Folder 31)
  - Smart, J. J. C., 1959 (Folder 32)
  - Sperry, Roger W., 1952-1969 (Folder 33)
  - Spiegelberg, Herbert, 1970 (Folder 34)
  - Stegmüller, Wolfgang, 1956-1966 (Reel 24, Folder 35)
  - Steven, Alan M., 1970 (Folder 36)
  - Stevens, S. S., 1966, 1970 (Folder 37)
  - Stoddard, George D., 1953-1954 (Folder 38)
  - Strawson, Peter, 1971 (Folder 39)
  - Suppes, Patrick, 1963 (Folder 40)
  - Teller, Paul, 1969 (Folder 41)
  - Terrell, D. B., 1966 (Folder 42)
  - Thalberg, I., 1963 (Folder 43)
  - Truesdell, Clifford, 1964 (Folder 44)
  - Turner, Joseph, 1955 (Folder 45)
  - Tyler, Ralph W., 1960 (Folder 46)
  - Vaihinger, Hans, 1921 (Folder 47)
  - Visscher, Maurice B., 1949, 1956 (Folder 48)
  - Waelder, Robert, 1938 (Folder 49)
  - Walker, Roland, 1954 (Folder 50)